spindistribute.com 2011-01-03

# Spin Distribute - Privacy Policy - Professional Article Distribution System

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit this website, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We might also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into your account.

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us.

[

1 article = 800+ backlinks

#### ARTICLE DISTRIBUTION

Publish 800+ unique versions of  
your article on 800+ websites! 

](http://www.spindistribute.com/ "Article Distribution - Distribute 800+ unique articles to 800+ websites") [

Let us do all the

#### ARTICLE WRITING

Need lots of keyword optimized  
quality articles? Search no more. 

](http://www.spindistribute.com/article-writing "Article Writing - We can write high quality articles for you") [

We suggest you our

#### COMPLETE SERVICE

We write articles. We distribute  
them. You get all the gains! 

](http://www.spindistribute.com/complete-service "Complete Service - We write and distribute 10 top quality articles for you")

##### Have any questions?

Feel free to check out the "Frequently Asked Questions" section, or use the email address below to contact our team. You can also register for free and contact our Support Department. [Read more](http://www.spindistribute.com/frequently-asked-questions "Frequently Asked Questions and Support")

Why choose

##### Spin Distribute?

**boost your traffic and online income** and crush your competitors with our great **article distribution system**

get **more than 800 highly relevant backlinks** with **each article distribution** (from $1.60 per distribution)

try out our **"Complete Service" that puts everything on auto-pilot** (we write & distribute articles for you)

have us **write all the articles for you** , so you can focus on your business

get **detailed HTML and PDF reports** for every article distribution

contact our **Support Department and Live Support** to get answers

get **FREE access to our SEO Tips & Tricks Guide (worth $27 alone!)**

join our **Affiliate Program and make money** with our services
